{
    "subject": "resource/Christopher_Koch",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tasmania",
    "human_readable": "Christopher Koch died in Tasmania.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7895328402519226,
            "question": "Where did Christopher Koch die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3205316364765167,
            "question": "Was Christopher Koch Australian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2450074404478073,
            "question": "What field was Christopher Koch known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1836455911397934,
            "question": "What is Tasmania known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1776130497455597,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks in Tasmania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13897407054901123,
            "question": "Did Christopher Koch make any significant contributions to science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11308347433805466,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Tasmania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10863421112298965,
            "question": "What is the geography like in Tasmania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09577018022537231,
            "question": "What are some of the cultural aspects of Tasmania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08995290100574493,
            "question": "Is Tasmania a popular tourist destination?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Christopher Koch died in Tasmania.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5851_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the cultural aspects of Tasmania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5851_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geography like in Tasmania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5851_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Tasmania?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5851_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5851_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I found that it supports the triple. Here is the response in the requested JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Christopher Koch passed away in Tasmania, with various articles stating his death location as Hobart, which is a city in Tasmania."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which mention that Christopher Koch passed away in Tasmania."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}